=The Truth=
=Episode 19=
The fatal injury
is a sharp-force puncture to the skull.
The shape and spacing match the features
of a push dagger.
Judging from the wound angle,
the killer had a height advantage
over the victim during the attack.
Numerous punctate marks
were found on the top of the head,
suspected to be multiple strikes
due to insufficient force.
If the victim is Ding Youcai,
could it be a carjacking?
No cash, phone, or similar items
were found among the pile of clothes.
So the suspect was likely a passenger
who hailed the taxi.
He killed the driver, robbed him,
stole the car, and buried the body.
Ding Youcai's car
belonged to the company.
He returned it after quitting.
Wang Tong, Liu Yang.
Talk to Ding Youcai's former colleagues.
Ye, let's visit his hukou location.
- Yes, sir.
- Yes, sir. Let's go.
Anything wrong,
Master?
You said your friend
could get the new
AD medication from abroad.
Give me your father's medical records.
Forget it if it's too troublesome.
It is troublesome.
Bring me the records.
Okay.
Thanks.
He's definitely Baldy Ding.
No doubt about it.
Ding Youcai.
Baldy Ding is his nickname.
He already had little hair
when he was young.
What happened to him?
We haven't heard from him
in the village for years.
Could you please
tell us about him in detail?
Okay.
Ding Youcai...
Let me get you some water.
He used to be idle and lazy,
and spent all day gambling.
Our village was demolished
a long time ago.
His family had two small houses,
but he squandered and lost them both.
His parents had only him, this one son.
They sold everything they had
to get him a wife.
But he remained unmotivated.
He was still going out
to fool around after he got married.
So his wife didn't get along with him.
They fought a lot.
Thanks.
A few times, it got really bad.
Even the local police came.
He beat his wife?
No, the other way around.
Ding Youcai's wife was fierce,
tall, and strong,
very intimidating.
Ding Youcai usually
got the worst end of their fights.
I'd say they're a perfect match.
But eventually, things calmed down.
Well,
apart from that,
his wife was quite decent.
She gave birth to their son
and took care of her in-laws
until they passed.
Ding Youcai had a son?
Yeah.
What's his name again?
Weren't Ding Youcai's wife and son
on the same hukou registration as him?
Ding Youcai's wife
came from the neighboring town.
Her surname was Yu, I think.
She had an urban hukou,
so the child was registered under her
to attend a better school in the county.
Now, it's called the "district."
This was good for the child,
but Ding Youcai wasn't happy about it.
He felt it made him lose face,
having the child register
under the mother.
He made a fuss about it several times.
But he couldn't convince his wife,
so he got angry and left to find work.
When did that happen?
Must be about twenty years ago.
His son, Ding Yu, is the same age
as my youngest daughter.
They're 25 now.
Where did he go to work?
I have no idea.
Did Ding Youcai
ever come back to the village?
Yes, he came back often.
He wouldn't do hard labor
and complained about everything.
H-He couldn't
hold down any job for long.
His wife felt she couldn't rely on him,
so she went to the city and found a job.
Then she took the child
to the city with her.
Can we still get in touch
with Ding Youcai's wife?
I'm not that capable.
She was cremated to ashes.
Ding Youcai's wife died of cancer.
Ding Yu was in middle school that year.
That's about 13 years ago.
What is this Ding Yu doing now?
I really have no idea.
Some say Ding Youcai took him away.
Others say he just gave him some money
and abandoned him.
But I did see him once later.
- Nice.
Thank you.
Come on, thanks, guys.
Come on.
Enjoy the food and drinks.
Enjoy.
Make yourselves at home.
Alright.
Sit.
Enjoy the food and drinks.
So Ding Youcai got remarried?
About nine or ten years ago.
He brought a woman back to the village
and held a wedding banquet.
He didn't ask me
to issue a marriage statement.
I don't know if they got registered.
Then what?
Then he took Ding Yu away.
Ding Yu wasn't good at studying.
He never got into high school.
He probably went to earn money
with his father.
What happened to the woman
Ding Youcai brought back
for the wedding banquet?
Well, that woman looked quite young.
She rarely spoke.
She didn't seem much older than Ding Yu.
We might've heard her name back then...
But it's been too long.
I-I've forgotten.
Thank you.
No problem.
We'll visit you again
if anything comes up.
Alright.
Anytime.
See you.
Okay.
We'll take this back with us.
See you.
Take care.
Go back inside.
Thanks.
Take care, officers.
Okay.
Hello?
Ye Qian.
We found something.
Hold on a second.
Go ahead.
We found traces of burnt tin foil
in the soil sample.
It should be
from the funeral paper ingots.
The killer burned spirit money
for the victim?
Who knows?
Maybe it was out of remorse.
Okay, got it.
Talk later.
Master.
We still have
too little information on Ding Youcai.
I think we should start with Ding Yu.
Ding Yu likely settled in town
with his mother.
I'll check his identity records.
You've completely
ruled out robbery-homicide?
I think the victim knew the killer.
Rural folks value their hometown.
That's why the body
was buried somewhere
near Ding Youcai's hometown.
The burnt spirit money
shows that the killer felt guilty.
And I think that CD
was deliberately placed there.
But I haven't figured out why yet.
Please take your belongings.
Okay.
Watch for cars.
Over here.
Baby.
I'm here.
Slow down.
Over here.
Xixi.
Come here.
Over here.
What did you learn today?
You can't remember?
Were you absent-minded?
No.
Really?
Really.
See anything you like?
You like balloons?
Put on your armor.
Let's get going.
Keep your legs in.
Sweetie.
Balloons aren't safe in the car.
Dad will tie it here for now.
Play with it when we get home, okay?
Is this fun?
Yes.
Hello, officers.
Fang Qihang, right?
Yes.
(Longxi Travels)
Police.
We have some questions.
Let me see your ID first.
Okay.
You run this travel agency?
Yeah.
I have my business license
right there on the wall.
I'm a law-abiding citizen.
I haven't done anything.
Then why'd I hear you
ran a matchmaking agency
for cross-border marriages?
Pretty trendy, huh?
No.
I completely stopped
the cross-border marriage service
almost ten years ago.
Really.
Officers, have a seat.
Come on.
Here.
Thanks.
Do you know Ding Youcai?
Y-Yes, I know him.
What's wrong?
What did he do?
Officer.
I don't know anything
about what he has done.
We haven't seen each other for years.
Not even a phone call.
But I heard you two were pretty close.
We used to drive taxis together
and spent all day gambling.
And we used to play cards, too.
That's how we got to know each other.
But that was nearly ten years ago.
Fang, not driving today?
I just got back.
Alright.
Nine of dots.
I won.
I let you win again? Here, take it.
Seven pairs.
Come on.
Ding.
Lucky streak today, huh?
Today I'm going to win big time.
I'm winning you today.
I've seen it too many times.
Changing players
is like changing blades.
I haven't won money off you in a while.
Well, that depends on your luck.
I'm going to win.
Not working today?
Too few customers in this heat.
We finally got a game together.
I've got to play to satisfy the itch.
Yeah.
Here, watch this.
Did he have any enemies?
Ding Youcai
was a pretty decent guy,
generous and loyal to friends.
As far as I know,
he got along well with everyone.
I wouldn't say he made enemies.
Did he love music
or singing?
He loved listening to Teresa Teng.
He'd hum her tunes all the time.
Red Dragon.
North Wind.
Alright.
So lucky.
How about that?
Pay up.
Here.
Unbelievable luck.
You always beat me when you come.
Watch me.
What are you doing?
The battle song sounds,
and money goes around.
Come on.
Watch me clean house today.
You know Ding Youcai had a son?
Yeah.
I've seen him a few times.
The two of them
took shifts driving the taxi.
Ding Youcai made his son drive the taxi?
A minor driving without a license?
Well, Ding Youcai's son
looked older than he was.
As long as he didn't speak,
he could easily pass for someone
in his early twenties.
Besides, driving isn't that hard.
It's all about practice.
A few more runs,
and he got the hang of it.
Straighten the wheel.
Like this.
Now shift into drive.
Yes, okay.
Come on, forward.
This way, come out.
Reverse. Turn the wheel.
Okay.
Back up.
Okay, slow down.
Back up, yeah.
Turn the wheel.
Yes, back up.
Keep going.
Were they close?
Well, he was a teenager.
They argued sometimes.
But the kid was quite sensible to me.
He took shifts for his dad
and seemed to have
several part-time jobs.
Ding Youcai had a girlfriend back then.
Did you know her?
Actually, I introduced her to him.
I was trying to switch careers.
Driving a taxi was too tough
and didn't pay well.
A friend had connections in this field,
so we partnered
and opened that matchmaking agency.
We made some money,
and it was good karma too.
I heard she was a foreign girl?
Look.
It was hard for a single dad
to raise a teenage son.
A man needs a wife
to look after him, right?
I tried finding him a local match first.
But he wouldn't settle
for someone "not good enough",
and the "good ones"
wouldn't look at him twice.
Plus, he insisted on someone
quiet and obedient,
nothing like his former wife.
Since I was doing
the cross-border service,
I found someone for him from abroad.
O-Officers,
I have some business to attend to later.
I have an appointment.
Can we continue this another day?
What's wrong? Uncomfortable in this car?
Not at all.
I'm a law-abiding citizen.
It's just my first time in a police car.
I-I'm a bit excited.
You're too kind,
giving me a ride and all.
Back to Ding Youcai's second wife.
Did she marry him willingly?
You followed the legal procedures?
Of course, she did.
I even took him across the border
to meet her family.
He handed the bride price
directly to her parents.
Everything was done by the book.
You charged a hefty fee?
Just the cost price.
A friend's discount, 100,000 RMB.
Tell me about the girl.
In detail.
I need to check my records for that.
It's been a long time.
I just remember
they gave her a Chinese name
when she arrived,
called Yu Meigui.
That's right.
Same surname as his late wife, I think.
The girl was 17 then.
Come on.
Don't give me that look.
That's considered late to marry
and have children where she's from.
But not here.
They had to wait a few years
to register the marriage.
Later, I stopped driving
and got busy with the business.
So I met with Ding Youcai less often.
Eventually, we lost contact completely.
Officers,
what happened to Ding Youcai?
It doesn't sound like he got in trouble.
More like something happened to him.
A set of remains was found.
We suspect it's Ding Youcai.
R-Remains?
If it's confirmed to be Ding Youcai,
then he died three years ago.
But I saw his son just last year.
It was quite a coincidence.
My car broke down that day.
I called a ride-hailing car.
That driver turned out to be his son.
Last four digits.
7482.
Aren't you Ding Youcai's son?
How is your dad doing?
He went back to his hometown.
Harder. Don't act like
you haven't eaten.
I brought some food.
I was thinking,
given the victim's height,
it's quite difficult
to cause such a wound
even if he was sitting down.
What if it's a car seat?
Haven't we already ruled out
the possibility of carjacking murder?
We got a message from the taxi company.
They checked the records.
Ding Youcai didn't
return the car or resign in person.
His son, Ding Yu, did it for him.
Ding Yu had his father's ID card.
He said Ding Youcai had business
and was back in his hometown
and asked him to handle it.
That makes Ding Yu highly suspicious.
Based on the injury
to the victim's skull,
if it happened in the car,
then he was sitting
in the passenger seat
or the right side of the back seat.
Can Ding Yu drive?
Yes.
He started driving taxis
in shifts with his father as a teenager.
Where was Ding Youcai's car found?
It could be the crime scene.
The taxi company said
that the car is almost at its scrap age,
but they haven't dealt with it.
They'll tow it over tomorrow.
Ding Yu is working in this city
as a ride-hailing driver.
We've already found
his address and contact information.
Master is probably almost there now.
What about Han Zhao?
Is she really going abroad?
Maybe.
I saw that post she made on Moments.
The shop has been transferred.
Haven't you been in contact?
We have.
Right now, I'm just focusing on my job
and waiting for her
as a friend.
(And this ring you've been wearing)
is made of plastic.
The paint is badly worn.
I speculate
he gave it to you when you played house
as kids.
This balloon carries the baby
into an unknown world.
With fear and curiosity,
the balloon floats and floats.
The baby runs hard.
He hasn't realized
that he has changed and grown.
Sleepy?
Go to sleep, okay?
Good night, Daddy.
Good night.
Be good.
Hello?
Ding Yu.
We're from CID.
CID officers?
What do you need from me?
You know why we're here for you, right?
We're right downstairs.
My child is home. He just fell asleep.
Whatever it is,
can we wait until tomorrow?
Ding Youcai.
You raise the kid alone?
Please keep it down.
Thank you.
Where's his mother?
We broke up.
You found my dad?
Why there?
It's close to the hometown.
He was superstitious,
always talking about
returning to his roots.
Too bad he didn't rest in a coffin.
Weren't you afraid of being discovered
burning spirit money in the night?
I was scared.
So I didn't dare burn too much.
You moved in with your dad
right after graduating from junior high?
Were you close?
Just so-so.
I heard you often argued.
I was young and simple-minded.
Then why did you kill him?
I-I didn't kill him.
I didn't kill my dad.
We came to see you today
because we have obtained evidence.
I-I'm telling the truth.
I admit, I buried the body.
But I didn't kill him.
When I got that call and rushed over,
he was already dead.
Explain then.
What call?
Not driving today?
I just got back.
(Ding Youcai)
(Cover my shift in South City.)
If you didn't kill him,
why didn't you call the police?
I was afraid
the police would suspect me.
What were you afraid of
if you didn't do anything?
My relationship with my dad
was always pretty tense.
I saw on TV and online
that whenever there's a homicide,
the police always suspect
people close to the victim.
Your relationship was tense?
Why?
He wronged my mom.
Even though we lived together,
I couldn't get over it.
Who called you then?
The call and text
were both from my dad's phone.
The call didn't go through.
The text just told me
to pick him up at that place.
But whether my dad sent it himself,
I don't know.
Then what?
Then I headed towards our hometown.
On the way, I bought
some spirit money and paper ingots.
Where did you buy those late at night?
I-I remember it was
a 24-hour funeral supply shop.
Near a hospital, I think.
What tool did you use to dig the hole?
A shovel.
(It was always in the trunk
of the taxi.)
(Because we often drove to the suburbs.)
(The roads were bad,)
(full of bumps and ditches.)
(The car could get stuck.)
(So we always kept a shovel.)
After that,
I found a place to wash the car,
returned it to the company,
and told them
my dad had gone back to our hometown.
This is the phone
my dad used at the time.
The number was canceled.
But I kept the phone.
I wanted to sell it second-hand.
If I go to jail,
my son...
No other relatives?
There are some on my mom's side,
but we haven't been in touch for years.
Your dad liked Teresa Teng?
That CD is genuine.
The limited edition is hard to get.
My mom liked her.
My dad liked listening to Teresa Teng
under the influence of my mom.
Back then, they got along pretty well.
My dad bought the CD himself.
It was always in his car.
He never even got to open it.
So I thought I'd save it for his trip.
Let's talk about Yu Meigui.
I wasn't close to her.
She left after my dad was gone.
Where did she go?
I don't know.
Probably home?
Did they register their marriage?
No.
She wasn't old enough
when she first came.
But three years ago,
she was in her twenties.
Why not register then?
That's between her and my dad.
How would I know?
How was their relationship?
Just so-so.
You lived together?
Money was tight,
renting one slightly bigger place.
How could we afford two?
So, to your knowledge,
did your dad ever abuse Yu Meigui?
She didn't have
friends or relatives here?
Some hometown fellows, maybe.
There were quite a few people like her.
But I'm not so sure.
Mr. Fang should know.
They seemed pretty close.
Fang Qihang?
Yeah.
They had gatherings
with their fellow people
at Mr. Fang's place.
Dad.
We woke you up, sweetie?
Come here.
Well...
These two uncles are Dad's friends.
We're talking about adult stuff.
You have to go to kindergarten tomorrow.
How about we go inside and sleep?
Be good.
Captain Leng, what do we do now?
What do you think?
Monitor him.
Yu Meigui's passport information,
entry and exit records,
and Fang Qihang's as well,
need to be thoroughly investigated.
Yeah.
Note it down.
Okay.
Captain Leng.
The logistics company
where Ding Yu worked three years ago
confirmed his employment information.
The entry and exit department
didn't find any exit record
of Ruan Shihong, aka Yu Meigui.
Her visa renewal procedures
were handled
by Fang Qihang's travel agency,
even after Ding Youcai's death.
And after Fang Qihang spoke with us,
he booked a flight
heading southwest tomorrow.
He's running away.
- Give my money back.
- I want my money.
- Where are you?
- Come out.
- Give my money back.
- Where are you?
Fang Qihang!
Open up.
What are you doing?
Pay up!
Police!
Police. We are police.
Put that down.
Perfect timing, sir.
Arrest that punk Fang Qihang.
He scammed all our money.
Fang Qihang.
Fang Qihang,
we're from the city police department.
Fang Qihang.
Fang Qihang, you've met Captain Leng.
I can't go out.
Those people want trouble.
They're blackmailing me
and threatening me.
Tell him to come out first.
Talk things through.
Fang Qihang.
No matter what dispute you have,
you can sit down and talk.
Fang Qihang.
They couldn't keep their foreign brides
and came here to make trouble.
They picked those girls themselves.
They arranged the marriages there.
They even slept together.
Now that the girls ran away,
they came to me.
It's not like I told them to run away.
I just organized a tour group
to go there.
It has nothing to do with me.
My son didn't even touch her.
That woman ran away
just two days after arrival.
We saved up half our lives
to buy a wife for our son.
She just vanished.
No grandchild for us now.
It's not just our family.
You're just a swindler
scamming money.
- We're the same!
- Give my money back.
He scammed all of us.
Put it down.
Put that down.
Notify the station.
Ask for some officers.
Yes, sir.
It's been three years.
This car must have been cleaned.
And it's a taxi.
Countless people have ridden in it.
So we have to be careful.
Even if there's nothing on the surface,
we'll definitely find clues
in the sponge or fabric.
Be careful.
♪Replacing the weight of tears
with that of sweat♪
♪Covering the gunshot's sound
with wounds♪
♪No one is born unyielding and strong♪
♪But because someone
always rushes ahead♪
♪To shield us from the storm♪
♪When every extraordinary act
becomes routine♪
♪Just to polish the badge
upon their shoulder♪
♪Like light surging unseen
through the night♪
♪Converging into your form♪
♪Looking up♪
♪Such dazzling glory♪
♪Like hope♪
♪Reaching out its arms♪
♪Cloaked in light♪
♪Alone, they charge ahead♪
♪Traversing♪
♪The battlefield of fate♪